http://www.4nsi.com/privacy-policy

Our Industrial X-ray Systems
We design & build 2D Digital Radiography and 3D Computed Tomography X-ray inspection systems. Our systems support additional features such as automated robotic scanning, precision metrology, 4D scanning, and more.
See All X-ray Systems
X-Ray Systems
X25
X3000
X5000
X7000
RobotiX
Manipulators
X3500
X5500
X7500
Upgrades & Addons
See All Innovations
Software
Our efX Software Suite including DR & CT X-ray viewing and analysis, DICONDE management, and more.
High performance image processing and measurement functions using GPU for faster acquisitions.
3D X-ray (CT) has never been easier with Automatic Parallelization for systems with multiple CPU’s and GPU’s, an Intuitive interface, and OpenGL based 3D volume rendering.
Our efX software is fully DICONDE compliant
Innovations
Each new innovation is designed to improve capabilities, increase speed, or create a solution the industry has never seen before.
Our CXMMs (Coordinate X-ray Measuring Machine) make use of non-contact and non-destructive technology that provides unique advantages compared to classical Coordinate Measuring Machines (CMMs).
Automated X-ray CT scanning systems make batch scanning and part loading and unloading effortless.
Improve resolution of images with a combination of hardware and a proprietary software algorithm.
Stitch multiple images together forming one seamless image with a much larger field of view.
Spiral acquisition and reconstruction with a digital flat-panel detector.
Reconstruct a complete 3D CT model that includes time and motion, creating a truly dynamic volumetric dataset.
Ring Reduction compensates for the irregular response of the detector pixels during a CT scan.
Markets
The uses of Digital Radiography and Computed Tomography are very diverse. There are few limits on what we can scan and what we can see; we’re working every day to push those limits.
Additive Manufacturing
Aerospace
Automotive
Castings
Dental
Electronics
Food
Manufacturing
Medical Devices
Military & Defense
Plastics
North Star Imaging’s Inspection Services Group provides real-time X-ray inspection and CT scanning services to verify the integrity of internal components, with quick turn around times.
2D X-ray Scanning
Realtime product analysis, failure analysis, live manipulation, product screening and much more
3D X-ray Scanning
Using X-ray to build a 3D model of your part we can then inspect it from any angle to isolate materials of different density and much more.
High Energy X-ray Scanning
Six million electron volts paired with proprietary scatter reduction technology; NSI’s MeVX6 has the power to get through your most difficult parts.
Maintenance & Technical Services
No matter where you are, we are at your service 24 hours a day. If it is not between 8 AM and 5 PM CST, leave a message and our on-call service technician will get back to you within 24 hours.
Contact Our Service Dept.
Call Us: +1-763-463-5658
Email Us: support@4nsi.com
Asia Service: +86 18516 332 893
Service Contact Form RMA Request
Preventative Maintenance
X-ray systems need regular maintenance to ensure that the X-ray set remains free from contamination.
X-Ray Components
We offer many types of Industrial X-ray Tubes and Detectors to meet your inspection needs.
menu
Language
French
Training
Technology
About
Videos
News
iCT 2020
VIRTUAL EVENT - Digital Imaging and Ultrasonics for NDT 2020
Additive Manufacturing for Aerospace & Space Conference
The ATS Testing Expo - "Exhibition has been postponed by the exhibit organizers. New date is still pending"
VIRTUAL EVENT - Nondestructive Evaluation of Aerospace Materials and Structures 2020
North Star Imaging Webinar
NDT Talks Webinar - NASA Exploring CT for Space
Aerospace Testing International NDT Roundtable Webinar
Instron Biomedical Testing Open House Webinar
Blog
Careers
Visitor Form
Contact
Privacy Policy
Customer Privacy Notice (last updated June, 8, 2018)This Customer Privacy Policy governs the collection, disclosure and use of personal information and data relating to potential and existing customers and users of our goods and services ("you") of North Star Imaging. This Customer Privacy Policy provides you with details about the personal information we collect from you, how we use your personal information, and your rights to control personal information we hold about you.
We are committed to your right to privacy and will only process personal information you provide to us in accordance with applicable data protection laws.
Please read this policy carefully as it explains the personal information we collect about you and how such personal information is handled. By your continued use of our services (including our websites), you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this Customer Privacy Policy in its entirety. If you do not agree to this Customer Privacy Policy in its entirety, you must not use our products or services. Please check back for updates regularly, as we may amend this Customer Privacy Policy from time to time.
If you have any questions about how we collect, store and use your personal information, please contact us by email at privacy@4nsi.com or write to us at the following address:
19875 S. Diamond Lake RoadRogers, Minnesota 55374USA
Information We CollectThe personal information that we may collect about you broadly falls into the following categories:
Your name;
Company Name;
Payment processing information;
Company or business postal address;
Company or business email address;
Business landline or mobile telephone number;
Delivery details;
As well as other non-sensitive personal information;
Your industry interests
Your job title or job role
Company business information
Top level demographic information
Analytics & RemarketingIf you use our websites, we may also collect information about you or your computer when you browse to allow you to use the services available, and also collect anonymous information about you or your computer for analysis to support continual improvements to our products and services.
Information Collected:
Time on site
Pages Visited
Depth of Scroll
Device used
Etc
Change Google data sharing optionsLinkedIn Privacy PolicyBing Privacy Policy
NewslettersWe use ConstantContact to create and manage email newsletters.
Information Collected:
Name
Email Address
Company Name
Training RegistrationsWe offer training classes and require registrants to submit personal information to manage those classes.
Information Collected:
Name
Company
Phone Number
Email Address
Class Registration
Seat / Coupon code if used
Payment Method (no credit card information is stored)
Order ID
Payments made for training registrations are processed by Moneris
(Acquired by Vantiv).
This transaction is done securely over an encrypted connection.
Moneris Privacy Policy
How we use your personal informationWe use the personal information that we collect about you to respond to your enquiries for payment processing, for the provision of goods and services to you or to the company that you represent, and for providing continuing product care such as warrant and technical support. We also process your personal information where we are required to do so by law, and for the exercise or defence of legal claims.
From time to time, we may contact you for research purposes, or to tell you about our special offers and other services in accordance with your contact preferences. Where appropriate, we will obtain your consent to do so. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided in any of those communications.
If we intend on using your personal information for any other purpose, we will let you know how we intend to use it when it is captured.
We will only process your personal information for the specific purposes listed above or for any other purposes specifically permitted by law. Your personal information will only be processed to the extent that it is necessary for the specific purposes listed above.
Our legal basis for processing your personal informationWe will only process your personal information where you have consented (which you may withdraw after giving it if we are relying on consent as a legal basis), in order to perform a contract with you, or where the processing is necessary for our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of others, for example, for market research purposes or, where you are an existing customer or user, to promote our goods and services.
How long we retain your personal informationWe will only retain personal information if it is required for a specific purpose. We have a statutory duty to keep certain records for a specified minimum period, for example personal information in relation to the purchase of a product or service from North Star Imaging. We will not retain any data that is not connected to the purchase of an North Star Imaging product or service for longer than [5 years]. We will also retain and use your personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Information that is no longer required for any valid business purpose, and that we are not required to keep pursuant to any applicable law, will be routinely destroyed by secure means.
We may share your personal information with the following categories of recipients:
Our group companies, third party services providers and partners who provide data processing services to us (for example, to support the delivery of, provide functionality on, or help to enhance the security of our Website), or who otherwise process personal information for purposes that are described in this Privacy Notice or notified to you when we collect your personal information.
Any competent law enforcement body, regulatory, government agency, court or other third party where we believe disclosure is necessary (i) as a matter of applicable law or regulation, (ii) to exercise, establish or defend our legal rights, or (iii) to protect your vital interests or those of any other person;
A potential buyer (and its agents and advisers) in connection with any proposed purchase, merger or acquisition of any part of our business, provided that we inform the buyer it must use your personal information only for the purposes disclosed in this Privacy Notice;
Any other person with your consent to the disclosure.
We may transfer your personal information to our associated entities and other members of our group of companies (including our parent company, Illinois Tool Works Inc., in the US).
Please be aware that countries outside of the European Economic Area (EEA) may not offer the same level of data protection as a country within the EEA. We ensure that we have a relevant data processing agreement in place with each third party outside the EEA to ensure they are compliant with privacy and data protection laws. We will make sure that any transfer of your personal information by us will be secured and/or encrypted for its protection.
How we protect your informationWe use reasonable and appropriate administrative, technical, and organizational measures to safeguard personal information against loss, theft and unauthorized uses, access, disclosure, modifications or destruction. Certain areas of our websites may be password protected. If you are a user of our websites and have a password, you can help to preserve your privacy by ensuring that you do not share your password with anyone else.
Choices you have about how we use your informationYou have the following rights under data protection laws:
If you wish to access, correct, update or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by contacting us using the contact details provided under the "How to contact us" heading below .
In addition, you can object to processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information or request portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact details provided under the "How to contact us" heading below.
You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time.
You can exercise this right by clicking on the "unsubscribe" or "opt-out" link in the marketing e-mails we send you.
To opt-out of other forms of marketing (such as postal marketing or telemarketing), then please contact us using the contact details provided under the "How to contact us" heading below.
Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time.
Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information.
For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.
These rights may not apply in some cases, including where we must comply with legal requirements, where it would violate the rights of someone other than the individual requesting access, or (in the case of your right to request access to your personal information) where the request is manifestly unfounded or excessive.
If you would like to request access to, correction, amendment, or deletion of your personal information, please contact us using one of the methods below. We may request specific information from you to confirm your identity. In certain circumstances, for instance if you request substantial copies of documents, we may charge a reasonable fee.
We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.
Updates to this Privacy Notice
We may update this Privacy Notice from time to time in response to changing legal, technical or business developments. When we update our Privacy Notice, we will take appropriate measures to inform you, consistent with the significance of the changes we make.
We will obtain your consent to any material Privacy Notice changes if and where this is required by applicable data protection laws.
You can see when this Privacy Notice was last updated by checking the “last updated” date displayed at the top of this Privacy Notice.
How to Contact UsIf you have a concern or complaint about privacy, confidentiality or the personal information handling practices of North Star Imaging, our employees or service suppliers, please contact:
North Star Imagining Data Protection Officer
19875 S. Diamond Lake Road
Rogers, Minnesota 55374
USA
(763) 312-8836
privacy@4nsi.com
Websites Governed by this Privacy Policy
4nsi.com
xrayinspectionservice.com
Recent News
NSI Introduces New Webinar Series - NDT Talks
New High Energy X-ray System Coming Soon
North Star Imaging's COVID-19 Response
Trade Shows and Events
North Star Imaging attends many trade shows, conferences, and events every year. Check out where we will be next!
Dec 10
NDT Talks Webinar - NASA Exploring CT for Space
Related Content
No related pages found.
View All
Event Calendar
Blog Articles
This site uses cookies and other tracking technologies to assist with navigation and your ability to provide feedback, analyze your use of our website, assist with our promotional and marketing efforts. See our Privacy Policy for more information
accept
